<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vladflore.tech</title>
    <link>https://vladflore.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on vladflore.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vladflore.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning Python as a Java developer - 2/</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2023/06/learning-python-as-a-java-developer-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2023/06/learning-python-as-a-java-developer-2/</guid>
      <description>This is the second part of the series &amp;ldquo;Learning Python as a Java developer&amp;rdquo;. If you are interested in the other ones, check the links below:&#xA;part one Learning resources Before going into the details of the second part, I want to enumerate some of the resources I used and I am still using to learn/brush up on Python, beside the ones I mentioned in the first part:&#xA;CS50’s Introduction to Programming with Python, 2022 - free/payed Practical Python Programming, a course by David Beazley - free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java 17</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2022/07/java-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2022/07/java-17/</guid>
      <description>Meet Java 17 Java&amp;hellip; what version is it? &amp;hellip;17 reached GA on 14.09.2021 and brought a bunch of new features, of which two are of more interest than the rest, at least for me. These are:&#xA;sealed classes pattern matching for switch (first preview) Java 17 is a LTS version.&#xA;Sealed classes Sealed classes came in Java 17 via JEP 409 and although the name says &amp;ldquo;sealed classes&amp;rdquo; , interfaces are also subject to being sealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Python as a Java developer - 1/</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2022/07/learning-python-as-a-java-developer-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2022/07/learning-python-as-a-java-developer-1/</guid>
      <description>Becoming a Pythonista If the term &amp;ldquo;pythonista&amp;rdquo; seems unusual or off-putting to you, rest assured that you are not the only one. Personally, I find the word somewhat amusing, and I had to look it up initially. After all, &amp;ldquo;Python programmer&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Python software engineer&amp;rdquo; would suffice, right? Regardless, this post is not about what we call individuals who work with Python; rather, it&amp;rsquo;s about sharing my experience of learning Python as a Java software engineer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi Internet,&#xA;this is Vlad writing and I welcome you to my corner of Internet where I share stuff about Software Engineering and Computer Science.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m not that big on talking about myself, so I&amp;rsquo;m just gonna keep it short and to the point:&#xA;Q: Who are you, Vlad?&#xA;A: Just a man on this planet, currently living in Spain and working as a software engineer. I love learning new things and challenging myself with new things, especially when it comes to Software Engineering and Computer Science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Animated 4</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/12/git-animated-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/12/git-animated-4/</guid>
      <description>This is the forth and last video in the Git Animated series. If you are interested in the other ones, check the links below:&#xA;part one part two part three Another way of integrating changes of a branch into another one is by performing a rebase. Instead of creating a new merge commit, as it happens when we merge two histories, a rebase will change the base of a branch from one commit to another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Animated 3</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/09/git-animated-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/09/git-animated-3/</guid>
      <description>This is the third video in the Git Animated series. If you are interested in the other ones, check the links below:&#xA;part one part two part four In this video we will merge two histories, master and feature, which have diverged at commit M2. As each of the branches got new commits from that divergent point, the feature branch cannot be integrated into the master branch using a fast-forward approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Animated 2</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/08/git-animated-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/08/git-animated-2/</guid>
      <description>This is the second video in the Git Animated series. If you are interested in the other ones, check the links below:&#xA;part one part three part four In this video you will see what happens when we merge two histories, specifically merging feature into master. The thing to note here is that the merge is a fast-forward one, this is possible when there are no further commits on the branch we branched off of, after the point of creating the new branch (in our case on the branch master after commit M2).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Animated 1</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/08/git-animated-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/08/git-animated-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first post and first video of the video series Git Animated. With this series I am trying to visually depict how different Git commands and actions look like, basically what happens behind them when you execute them.&#xA;If you are interested in the other videos, please check the links below:&#xA;part two part three part four Note: if you are a software engineer and have never heard of Git, then this post, and the future ones, are not for you&amp;hellip;and I am also sorry for you!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first OSS PR</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/07/my-first-oss-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/07/my-first-oss-pr/</guid>
      <description>Software developers write code&amp;hellip;or at least they should, provided they can escape the long boring meetings which finish with no conclusions or, God forbid, with the next appointment&amp;hellip;to discuss more.&#xA;When we monetize this action of writing code, we usually do it as part of a job, which comes with its pros and cons, and such we have to stay in the legal framework of that working contract. This legal framework might very well prevent us from contributing to Open Source Software(OSS), so make sure to read the fine print!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nine Months Later</title>
      <link>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/05/nine-months-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vladflore.tech/posts/2021/05/nine-months-later/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR&#xA;&amp;hellip;if you were thinking about screaming little humans, I am afraid I will disappoint you and it might be that this post is not for you.&#xA;If you are still reading, then you might be one of those people, who thought of something else what could have happened in a period of nine months. I salute you and encourage you to read on!&#xA;2020 was a special year, for the world and for me as well, on one side we had that end of the world kind of global infestation thing, on the other side I managed to make some changes, which hopefully will pay-off in the near future, dare saying some of them have already payed-off.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
